

CONTACTS

tetiross@gmail.com +380-68-05-333-83 Ternopil, Ukraine tetiross.github.io

EDUCATION

Ternopil State 'Ivan Pul'uj' Technical University

Masters Degree in Computer Science

LANGUAGES

English - Advanced Ukrainian - Native

ROSTYSLAV **SEMANYSHYN**

PROFILE

Ruby on Rails developer with 6+ years of commercial experience. Worked on a different kind of projects including: healthcare, social networks, finance, datings, e-commerce etc.

I care about clients business and not just thoughtlessly do tasks but always think about the problem that they should solve and therefore the best ways to implement solution.

Spent 4 months living and working in the USA.

WORK EXPERIENCE

N-iX (Seeking Alpha) | Jul. 2021 - Present | Remote

Ruby on Rails Backend Developer

• taking part in developing features and updating current architecture to improve main system processes

Technologies: Ruby on Rails, Ruby, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, Sphinx

Crunch (Saleship) | Aug. 2019 - Jul. 2021 | Remote

Ruby on Rails Full Stack Developer / Project Lead Developer

- maintaining and developing E-Commerce application built on multiple microservices
- managing team
- improving development process
- working with different martkeplaces API
- setting up and managing servers for core application and microservices

Technologies: Ruby on Rails, Ruby, Vue.js, PostgreSQL, Git, Amazon MWS API.

MLSDev | Feb. 2017 - Aug. 2019 | Remote

Ruby on Rails Backend Developer

- developing MVP projects in a variety of spheres (healthcare, e-commerce, dating, social networks, etc.)
- direct communication with clients
- performing code reviews
- developing local template project, and reusable solutions

Technologies: Ruby on Rails, Ruby, PostgreSQL, Redis, RabbitMQ, Git, AWS services (S3, Lambda, CloudWatch, MediaConvert).

Hmarynka Studio | Oct. 2015 - Dec. 2016 | Ternopil, Ukraine

Ruby on Rails Full Stack Developer

- improving skills by working under a mentorship of experienced developer
- solely developing full stack finance project for US market
- performing local presentations

Technologies: Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, HTML/CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Heroku, Git.